marinedepot.com 2015-06-07

# MarineDepot.com

This privacy statement covers the site [http://www.marinedepot.com](http://www.marinedepot.com/).

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact [customercare@MarineDepot.com](mailto:customercare@MarineDepot.com).

## Information Collection and Use

MarineDepot.com is the sole owner of information collected on this site to purchase products and services from MarineDepot.com. We will not sell, share or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, email address and payment information, such as your credit/debit card number. You have the option of creating an account with a username and password for future access to your account information and order history. To safeguard your username and password, DO NOT share them with anyone. If you do not want to create an account (for instance, if you are buying a gift for a friend), you may checkout as a guest. You will still be required to provide information relevant for processing your order but do not need to create a username and password for future visits. 

## Registration

You have the option of registering for an account while placing an order with us. Having an account is useful if you intend to place future orders or use advanced store functionality, like writing product reviews. Accountholders can track orders on our website, save their shopping cart, check order history, setup returns and store multiple shipping addresses. Information collected during account registration and checkout includes first and last name, billing and shipping address, email address and telephone number. This information is used to provide you with important MarineDepot.com services such as automated order status updates via email. 

## Orders

Information collected during registration and checkout is used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order, wire transfer or check information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use your contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. See the Security section below for more details on security measures and procedures. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Sharing section of this policy. 

## Cookies

We customize certain web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. If you choose to reject the cookie, you can still browse our store but will be unable to use the shopping cart to buy merchandise. The MarineDepot.com shopping cart cannot function without cookies enabled because your personal information will not be retained to process your order. MarineDepot.com is unable to accept online orders with cookies enabled. Rest assured we will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party. We may link data stored in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. This allows us to personalize your shopping experience and discern user preferences. If you would like to buy from MarineDepot.com but are not comfortable placing your order online you may contact us toll-free and we’ll place the order for you over the telephone. 

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties. 

## Sharing

We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and email delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes. 

FedEx Corporation  
942 South Shady Grove Road  
Memphis, TN 38120  
1-800-GO-FEDEX  

UPS Corporate Headquarters  
55 Glenlake Parkway NE  
Atlanta, GA 30328  
1-800-PICK-UPS  

US Postal Service Headquarters  
475 L'Enfant Plaza SW  
Washington DC 20260  
1-800-ASK-USPS  

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

## Security

MarineDepot.com takes every precaution necessary to protect your privacy and personal information. When submitting sensitive information (such as a credit card number) via our website, that information is collected, encrypted and protected by the best encryption technology available in the industry—SSL. We combine secure servers with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) transmission to safeguard the personal information of all MarineDepot.com customers. What this means is that any time you send data to our web server it will be encrypted and, in turn, our server will encrypt any data sent back to your web browser. MarineDepot.com uses 128-bit encryption by VeriSign, the most advanced form of SSL software presently available. MarineDepot.com online shopping cart uses VeriSign Digital IDs (SSL Secure Certificate) exclusively. To learn more about SSL, please visit [www.verisign.com](http://www.verisign.com/). 

## Correction/Updating/Reviewing Personal Information

Registered customers may change or review their stored account information (such as street address or email address) through our website by entering My Account. You must have your username and password in order to access your account. In the event you forget both your username and password, please contact our customer service department for assistance. 

## Choice/Opt-out

If you receive a marketing email from MarineDepot.com and would prefer to not receive these types of messages, click the "unsubscribe" link in the email footer to remove your name from our list. You may also opt-out by visiting our newsletter subscription page found in your account dashboard. 

## Notice of Changes

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

## Last Update

The Privacy Policy contained herein became officially effective January 1, 2010.
